There are many ways we can enjoy sport – watching it on TV or a smartphone, attending an event at a stadium or even playing the game.
我们有很多种享受体育运动的方式——在电视或智能手机上观看赛事、去体育场亲临现场观赛，甚至亲自上场参与。
But for those who enjoy getting competitive with their computer gaming, there are realistic-looking games with lifelike graphics to be played without leaving home.
但对于那些喜欢在电脑游戏中一较高下的人来说，足不出户就能玩到画面逼真、场景写实的游戏。
It’s this type of sport – if that’s what we can call it – that has become big business. And interest in it has gone to a new level.
正是这类活动——如果我们能将其称作体育运动的话——已经发展成了一项庞大的产业，人们对它的关注度也达到了全新高度。
Initially, grabbing a joystick or controller and playing a game was a solitary activity.
最初，手握游戏摇杆或手柄打游戏还是一项单人活动。
But around 20 years ago computers became cheaper and the internet became faster, which made it much easier for more people to get involved with computer gaming.
但大约20年前，电脑价格下降，网络速度提升，这让更多人更容易地参与电脑游戏。
This led to gamers connecting with each other around the world, so they could go head-to-head online.
这使得全球的玩家能够相互联接，在线上展开对决。
It also became a spectator sport, with people watching others play.
同时，观看他人打游戏也成了一项观赏性活动。
The whole experience has been given the name ‘esports’ – electronic sports.
这种全新的体验被命名为“电子竞技”。
Now, huge esports tournaments take place all over the world in big arenas with large crowds.
如今，大型电子竞技赛事在全球各地的大型场馆举办，现场座无虚席。
Die-hard enthusiasts, who have become first-rate players, are now well-known - some play together in teams.
那些痴迷电竞的爱好者蜕变成了顶尖选手，如今已经声名远扬——部分选手还组建了战队并肩作战。
Its top stars can earn millions of dollars a year, without even breaking into a sweat!
电竞领域的顶级明星每年能赚数百万美元，而且全程毫不费力！
And fans from around the world tune in to watch the action online.
全球的粉丝都会在线收看赛事直播。
The global audience is now estimated at more than 200 million and growing.
目前，电竞的全球观众数量估计已超过2亿，并且还在持续增长。
Annual revenues from esports, currently around 650 million dollars for events, continue to rise with billions more generated through video games sales.
电竞赛事的年收入目前约为6.5亿美元，这一数字仍在上升，此外视频游戏销售还能带来数十亿美元的额外收入。
Famous football clubs are now trying to get in on the action.
知名足球俱乐部如今也纷纷涉足电竞领域。
England’s Football Association for example launched its first esports team this year, known as the eLions.
例如，英格兰足球总会今年成立了首支电竞战队，名为“电子雄狮队”。
It recruited Fifa 19 players to represent them at the inaugural Fifa eNations Cup.
该协会招募了《FIFA 19》的玩家，代表球队参加首届国际足联电竞国家杯。
Mark Bullingham, the FA's chief commercial and football development officer, said "The FA prides itself on being a modern, innovative organisation that strives to engage and inspire all generations of football fans."
英格兰足总首席商务与足球发展官马克·布林厄姆表示：“英格兰足总始终以自身是一个现代化、富有创新精神的组织为荣，我们致力于吸引并激励每一代足球迷。”
But while this virtual version of football might give aspiring footballers a chance to get closer to the real game, some might argue the lack of physical activity means it shouldn’t be called a sport – and the biggest winners are the companies who promote and sell esports.
尽管这种虚拟足球能让怀揣足球梦的人们离真实的足球赛事更近一步，但有些人认为，电竞缺乏身体运动，因此不应被归类为体育运动——而最大的赢家其实是那些推广和经营电竞产业的公司。